

#### **PROFILE**

I'm a student of the CSE Department, and currently, we are under our mentor institute IIT Hyderabad. I always try to learn things through practical implementation along with deep theoretical knowledge. At present, I'm trying to learn things from IITH activities. I am also the Web Development Member at IIIT Raichur and Training and Placement Cell, IIIT Raichur. I have working experience with C, Object-Oriented Programming in C++ and JavaScript, HTML and CSS, Bootstrap, Jekyll, React Js, Express, MongoDB and several more Open Source Libraries like AOS, Particle Js, Owl Carousel. I have earned some skill badges you can see them on LinkedIn and you can see my Some open projects in GitHub

#### CONTACT

DATE OF BIRTH: 23rd May, 2003

LOCATION: Rajahmundry, Andhra Pradesh India

PHONE: +91 9492993737

WEBSITE:

https://koushikpuppala.live

EMAIL:

koushikpuppala203@gmail.com

# KOUSHIK PUPPALA

**CSE Engineering** 

# **EDUCATION**

#### Indian Institute of Information Technology

Dec, 2020 – Present (Bachelor of Technology - BTech, Computer Science)

#### Tirumala Junior College

2018 - 2020 (12th Class BIEAP M.P.C)

- Got 9.8 CGPA

# Tirumala Proactive EM High School

2017 - 2018 (10th Class BSEAP)

- Got 9.5 CGPA

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# Training and Placement Cell, IIIT Raichur [ Full Stack Developer]

Aug, 2021 - Present

- Contributed in the making of main Websites

# Indian Institute of Information Technology, Raichur [ Computer Science Engineer]

Dec, 2020 - Present

Contributed in the making of main Websites

### **SKILLS**

